I don't
أنا لا
Li Youen talks to everyone else but me.
لي يوين تتحدث مع الجميع إلا أنا.
Why do I say everything that comes to mind?
لماذا أقول كل ما يخطر ببالي؟
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
Do you want to take a day off today?
هل ترغب في أخذ إجازة اليوم؟
Why aren't you saying anything?
لماذا لا تقول شيئاً؟
Are you feeling unwell?
هل تشعر بتوعك؟
I'm going to training.
سأذهب إلى التدريب.
I have something to give you.
لدي شيء أريد أن أقدمه لك.
Aren't you going to open it and see?
ألن تفتحها وترى؟
You see for yourself.
سترى بنفسك.
Or you can say it.
أو يمكنك قول ذلك.
Or I can say it.
أو يمكنني أن أقولها.
We definitely have to tell the coach about this.
علينا بالتأكيد إخبار المدرب بهذا الأمر.
Medial epicondylitis at such a young age.
التهاب اللقيمة الإنسية في هذه السن المبكرة.
Do you think this is a joke?
هل تعتقد أن هذا مزحة؟
Who told you to wear elbow pads?
من قال لك أن ترتدي واقيات للمرفقين؟
You want the whole world to know?
أتريد أن يعلم العالم أجمع؟
Your elbow has a problem, right?
مرفقك يعاني من مشكلة، أليس كذلك؟
Instructor Ren, Instructor Ren.
المدرب رين، المدرب رين.
Two bone fragments
شظيتان عظميتان
How can you generate force with elbows like that?
كيف يمكنك توليد القوة باستخدام المرفقين بهذه الطريقة؟
Do you think
هل تعتقد
I have any reason to waste my time
هل لدي أي سبب لأضيع وقتي؟
on a cripple like you?
على شخص معاق مثلك؟
Do you like it?
هل أحببت ذلك؟
Why did you give this to me?
لماذا أعطيتني هذا؟
To mock me?
هل تسخر مني؟
No
لا
I
أنا
Try it
جرب
I made this myself
لقد صنعت هذا بنفسي
It still has my
لا يزال يحتفظ بي
Take it further away from me.
أبعده عني أكثر.
You want me to wear this?
هل تريدني أن أرتدي هذا؟
To tell everyone I have a problem with my elbow?
هل أخبر الجميع أن لدي مشكلة في مرفقي؟
Right?
يمين؟
That's not what I meant.
لم يكن هذا ما قصدته.
I just wanted to
أردت فقط أن
What did you want?
ماذا كنت تريد؟
Li Youen
لي يوين
I've told you more than once
لقد أخبرتك أكثر من مرة
not to do these unnecessary things.
عدم القيام بهذه الأشياء غير الضرورية.
Teacher Li
المعلمة لي
Why are you out here alone in the rain?
لماذا أنت هنا وحدك تحت المطر؟
Have some cake.
تناول بعض الكعك.
You'll feel a bit better.
ستشعر بتحسن طفيف.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Why are you out here alone in the rain?
لماذا أنت هنا وحدك تحت المطر؟
I think I
أعتقد أنني
upset him.
أزعجه ذلك.
Qiuyu Ge
كيويو جي
Teacher Li
المعلمة لي
You don't need to take it too much to heart
لا داعي لأن تأخذ الأمر على محمل الجد
Qiuyu Ge's anger
غضب Qiuyu Ge
comes and goes quickly
يأتي ويذهب بسرعة
Yeah
نعم
With the competition approaching
مع اقتراب موعد المنافسة
he must be under a lot of pressure
لا بد أنه يتعرض لضغوط كبيرة
That's true
هذا صحيح
I've been looking for you for a while
كنت أبحث عنك منذ فترة
You guys
يا رفاق
had plans?
هل كانت لديك خطط؟
We
نحن
are
نكون
helping Teacher Zhou film some material recently.
ساعدتُ المعلم تشو في تصوير بعض المواد مؤخراً.
Good friends
أصدقاء جيدون
help each other.
ساعدوا بعضكم بعضاً.
Then you guys go ahead.
ثم انطلقوا أنتم.
Teacher Li,
المعلمة لي،
then you alone?
إذن أنت وحدك؟
Are you still filming or not?
هل ما زلت تصور أم لا؟
Wait for me
الانتظار لي
Teacher Li
المعلمة لي
See you tomorrow!
أراك غداً!
Don't be angry
لا تغضب
I didn't mean anything else just now
لم أقصد أي شيء آخر الآن
Teacher Li doesn't know about our relationship yet
لا يعلم المعلم لي بعلاقتنا حتى الآن
I just haven't found the right opportunity to say it
لم أجد الفرصة المناسبة لأقول ذلك.
What's a suitable opportunity?
ما هي الفرصة المناسبة؟
Now it seems like I'm forcing you
الآن يبدو أنني أجبرك
No, no, no
لا، لا، لا
The atmosphere in the club has been tense lately
كان الجو متوتراً في النادي مؤخراً.
Teacher Li and Brother Qiu Yu seem to have had another conflict
يبدو أن المعلم لي والأخ تشيو يو قد دخلا في خلاف آخر
I'm afraid I'll disturb everyone.
أخشى أن أزعج الجميع.
Right.
يمين.
You all seem busy.
يبدو أنكم جميعاً مشغولون.
I have a new exhibition coming up.
لدي معرض جديد قادم.
I'll be busy preparing for it too.
سأكون مشغولاً بالتحضير لذلك أيضاً.
We'll all be busy together.
سنكون جميعاً مشغولين معاً.
You just take care of your club.
كل ما عليك فعله هو الاهتمام بناديك.
Zhou Song.
تشو سونغ.
It's getting cold.
الجو بدأ يبرد.
Wear more clothes.
ارتدي المزيد من الملابس.
Qiu Yu, watch the game.
تشيو يو، شاهد المباراة.
Teacher Li
المعلمة لي
Sit down.
اجلس.
I just remembered I forgot to bring something.
تذكرت للتو أنني نسيت إحضار شيء ما.
Teacher Li,
المعلمة لي،
Could you come here for a moment?
هل يمكنك المجيء إلى هنا للحظة؟
Zhai Qiuyu,
تشاي كيويو,
I'll help you take a look.
سأساعدك في إلقاء نظرة.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Really.
حقًا.
It's just that the training yesterday was a bit intense.
الأمر فقط أن التدريب بالأمس كان مكثفاً بعض الشيء.
It's not that bad.
الأمر ليس بهذا السوء.
Okay.
تمام.
If you feel any discomfort, report it immediately.
إذا شعرت بأي انزعاج، فأبلغ عنه على الفور.
Don't push yourself.
لا تجهد نفسك.
You
أنت
Xiao Gu
شياو جو
If you unintentionally
إذا قمت بذلك عن غير قصد
accidentally
عن طريق الخطأ
offend someone with your words
قد تُسيء إلى شخص ما بكلماتك
what do you do?
ماذا تفعل؟
Apologize, of course.
أعتذر بالطبع.
Just say sorry?
هل يكفي أن تقول آسف؟
Yeah.
نعم.
But if you were really out of line,
لكن إذا كنت قد تجاوزت حدودك حقاً،
apologizing won't help.
الاعتذار لن يجدي نفعاً.
Then what?
ثم ماذا؟
I don't know anymore.
لم أعد أعرف.
Maybe
ربما
after some time has passed,
بعد مرور بعض الوقت،
naturally,
بطبيعة الحال،
we'll make up.
سنتصالح.
Right.
يمين.
Then let's wait for time to pass.
فلننتظر إذن مرور الوقت.
Brother,
أخ،
come meet my new friend.
تعالَ قابل صديقي الجديد.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
I'm Chen Mo.
أنا تشين مو.
I came to the hospital to visit a friend today.
جئت إلى المستشفى اليوم لزيارة صديق.
I happened to see Xiao Si alone
صادفت رؤية شياو سي بمفردها
standing downstairs in the sun.
واقفاً في الطابق السفلي تحت أشعة الشمس.
The midday sun is quite strong.
شمس الظهيرة قوية جداً.
Patients are physically weak
المرضى ضعفاء جسدياً
and not suited to being in the sun for too long.
وغير مناسبة للتعرض لأشعة الشمس لفترة طويلة.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
شكراً لك يا سيد تشين.
You,
أنت،
brother,
أخ،
aren't you listening to the doctor again
ألا تستمع إلى الطبيب مجدداً؟
and refusing to leave?
ورفض المغادرة؟
I listen to Chen Mo.
أستمع إلى تشين مو.
Chen Mo knows so much.
تشين مو يعرف الكثير.
He even knows how to give massages.
بل إنه يعرف كيف يقدم خدمات التدليك.
Yes
نعم
I've learned some basics
لقد تعلمت بعض الأساسيات
The basics
الأساسيات
Didn't you tell me
ألم تخبرني؟
Are you a team doctor for tennis players?
هل أنت طبيب فريق لاعبي التنس؟
That's right, bro
هذا صحيح يا أخي
You two are in the same profession
أنتما تعملان في نفس المهنة
A team doctor for tennis players
طبيب فريق للاعبي التنس
I wouldn't say we're in the same profession
لا أظن أننا نعمل في نفس المهنة
I just have some experience
لدي بعض الخبرة فقط
You know
أنت تعرف
Athletes' temperaments
مزاج الرياضيين
Are mostly eccentric
معظمهم غريبون الأطوار
My job was also difficult
كانت وظيفتي صعبة أيضاً
So I changed careers later
لذلك غيرت مساري المهني لاحقاً
Then I'm luckier.
إذن أنا أكثر حظاً.
My athlete
رياضيي
isn't also a peculiar person?
أليس شخصًا غريب الأطوار أيضًا؟
Xiao Si,
شياو سي,
hurry up and eat.
أسرعوا وتناولوا الطعام.
Okay.
تمام.
You guys eat.
كلوا أنتم.
I won't disturb you.
لن أزعجك.
See you next time.
إلى اللقاء في المرة القادمة.
Goodbye, Chen Mo.
وداعاً، تشين مو.
Stop chatting with strangers.
توقف عن الدردشة مع الغرباء.
Is Chen Mo not a good person?
أليس تشين مو شخصًا جيدًا؟
Let's eat.
هيا نأكل.
It's been almost two weeks.
لقد مرّ أسبوعان تقريباً.
He really hasn't said a word.
لم ينطق بكلمة واحدة.
Coach,
مدرب،
Is Gu Hao not here today?
أليس غو هاو موجوداً هنا اليوم؟
Gu Hao?
قو هاو؟
He's not here today, is he?
إنه ليس هنا اليوم، أليس كذلك؟
I didn't see him.
لم أره.
Thanks, Coach.
شكراً لك يا مدرب.
Okay.
تمام.
What's that look?
ما هذه النظرة؟
You're stumped.
أنت عاجز عن الإجابة.
Likewise.
على نفس المنوال.
You're not doing much better.
أنت لست أفضل حالاً بكثير.
Your silver tongue
لسانك الفضي
hit a wall?
هل اصطدمت بجدار؟
I need a favor.
أحتاج إلى خدمة.
A trade.
صفقة تجارية.
You help me out too.
أنت تساعدني أيضاً.
Deal.
اتفاق.
Gu Hao
قو هاو
Come out.
يخرج.
I have a promotional photo for you to take.
لدي صورة ترويجية يمكنك التقاطها.
Let's talk.
هيا نتحدث.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm working.
أنا أعمل.
Working?
عمل؟
Who are you working with?
مع من تعمل؟
Did you and Brother Qiu Yu plan this?
هل خططت أنت والأخ تشيو يو لهذا الأمر؟
Did you find a suitable opportunity?
هل وجدت فرصة مناسبة؟
I
أنا
You're hurting me.
أنت تؤلمني.
It's just an opportunity.
إنها مجرد فرصة.
Is it that hard to find?
هل من الصعب العثور عليه؟
You
أنت
You're not going to cry, are you?
لن تبكي، أليس كذلك؟
I
أنا
Half a month.
نصف شهر.
You never even thought about looking for me,
لم تفكر حتى في البحث عني،
did you?
هل فعلت ذلك؟
Didn't you ask me to take care of the club first?
ألم تطلب مني الاهتمام بالنادي أولاً؟
I
أنا
You'll listen to whatever I say
ستستمع إلى كل ما أقوله
So I told you to find an opportunity
لذلك طلبت منك أن تجد فرصة
Why didn't you listen?
لماذا لم تستمع؟
You're the one who told me to
أنت من طلب مني ذلك
Why are you angrier than I am?
لماذا أنت أكثر غضباً مني؟
I'll tell them
سأخبرهم
Last time, I really hadn't thought it through
في المرة الماضية، لم أكن قد فكرت في الأمر جيداً.
Teacher Li suddenly appeared
ظهر المعلم لي فجأة
I wasn't prepared at all
لم أكن مستعداً على الإطلاق
And last time I didn't look for you
وفي المرة الأخيرة لم أبحث عنك
I hadn't figured out how to explain it to you
لم أكن قد توصلت إلى طريقة لشرح ذلك لك
You don't need to look for me, of course.
بالطبع لست بحاجة للبحث عني.
We're just good friends anyway.
نحن مجرد أصدقاء مقربين على أي حال.
Does it even matter if you look or not?
هل يهمّ إن نظرت أم لا؟
How about this then?
ما رأيك بهذا إذن؟
I'll take you to the club right now.
سآخذك إلى النادي الآن.
And tell everyone about our relationship.
وأخبر الجميع عن علاقتنا.
Zhou Song,
تشو سونغ,
look at me.
انظر إليَّ.
Look at me, look at me!
انظر إليّ، انظر إليّ!
Who taught you all this?
من علمك كل هذا؟
Are you crazy?
هل أنت مجنون؟
Even if I told you, you wouldn't understand.
حتى لو أخبرتك، فلن تفهم.
Go on.
هيا.
What do you need my help with?
في ماذا تحتاج مساعدتي؟
Me?
أنا؟
I haven't had a massage recently.
لم أحصل على جلسة تدليك مؤخراً.
Then go find Li Youen.
ثم اذهب وابحث عن لي يوين.
What good am I to you?
ما فائدتي لك؟
You had a fight
لقد تشاجرتما
and offended Teacher Li.
وأثار ذلك غضب المعلمة لي.
Zhai Qiuyu,
تشاي كيويو,
you're not being human again.
أنت لم تعد إنساناً.
You're indecisive.
أنت متردد.
This won't help you.
هذا لن يفيدك.
Waiting for others to run around for you every day,
في انتظار أن يقوم الآخرون بالركض من أجلك كل يوم،
while you do nothing.
بينما أنت لا تفعل شيئاً.
If you can win her back like this,
إذا استطعت استعادتها بهذه الطريقة،
then I'll be impressed.
حينها سأكون منبهراً.
You left.
لقد رحلت.
Without even a thank you.
حتى بدون كلمة شكر.
He's even started learning to cook
بل إنه بدأ يتعلم الطبخ
Does that mean he doesn't need me to take care of him anymore?
هل هذا يعني أنه لم يعد بحاجة إليّ لأعتني به؟
Guys
شباب
A friend brought some special medicine from abroad
أحضر صديق بعض الأدوية الخاصة من الخارج
Everyone, take some
الجميع، خذوا بعضاً
Let's take precautions
لنتخذ الاحتياطات اللازمة
Thanks
شكرًا
Did Zhai Ge take the wrong medicine?
هل تناول تشاي غي الدواء الخاطئ؟
I don't know
لا أعرف
He's started focusing on his health
لقد بدأ يركز على صحته
So he's not planning to use the medicine I prepared anymore?
إذن فهو لا ينوي استخدام الدواء الذي أعددته بعد الآن؟
He's not here.
إنه ليس هنا.
He said he needs to rest regularly.
قال إنه يحتاج إلى الراحة بانتظام.
Where is this dye shop?
أين يقع محل الصباغة هذا؟
The dye shop.
محل الصباغة.
Did he go alone?
هل ذهب بمفرده؟
I think so.
أعتقد ذلك.
He doesn't even need me
إنه لا يحتاجني حتى
for rest anymore.
للراحة بعد الآن.
He's just my boss.
إنه مجرد رئيسي.
I'm here to make money.
أنا هنا لأجني المال.
I don't need to think about useless things.
لا داعي للتفكير في أشياء عديمة الفائدة.
I just need to focus on my work.
كل ما أحتاجه هو التركيز على عملي.
Li Youen
لي يوين
Brother Qiu Yu
الأخ تشيو يو
You and Teacher Li haven't made up yet.
لم تتصالحي أنتِ والمعلمة لي بعد.
Teacher Li
المعلمة لي
You and Brother Qiu Yu haven't made up yet.
لم تتصالحي أنتِ والأخ تشيو يو بعد.
I'll try to stay away from him.
سأحاول الابتعاد عنه.
It won't affect his competition.
لن يؤثر ذلك على منافسيه.
Zhou Song and I have so many ideas,
لدي أنا وتشو سونغ الكثير من الأفكار،
but none of them are useful.
لكن لا أحد منهم مفيد.
Skin patch
رقعة جلدية
Painkillers
مسكنات الألم
Elastic bandage
ضمادة مرنة
What else are you trying to teach me?
ماذا تحاول أن تعلمني أيضاً؟
You won't call me until the competition starts.
لن تتصل بي حتى تبدأ المنافسة.
What's your attitude?
ما هو موقفك؟
Your elbow injury is common knowledge, and yet...
إصابة مرفقك معروفة للجميع، ومع ذلك...
...you still have the nerve to yell at me?
...ما زلت تملك الجرأة لتصرخ في وجهي؟
I know you don't want others to know about my old injury.
أعلم أنك لا تريد أن يعرف الآخرون عن إصابتي القديمة.
There's no need to emphasize it every time.
لا داعي للتأكيد على ذلك في كل مرة.
The injury is your own fault.
الإصابة هي خطأك أنت.
Why are you competing with me?
لماذا تنافسني؟
And yet you're the one feeling wronged.
ومع ذلك فأنت من يشعر بالظلم.
You really haven't changed at all.
أنت لم تتغير على الإطلاق.
Stop being so sarcastic.
توقف عن السخرية.
I have only one thing to say.
ليس لدي سوى شيء واحد لأقوله.
No matter how much it hurts,
مهما كان الألم شديداً،
you all have to stand firm on the court.
يجب عليكم جميعاً أن تثبتوا في الملعب.
You're really something else as a mother.
أنتِ حقاً أم مميزة.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
I said, of course I will.
قلت: بالطبع سأفعل.
Even if it hurts like hell,
حتى لو كان الأمر مؤلماً للغاية،
I will stand on the court.
سأقف في الملعب.
I only went to him because I was really uncomfortable.
لم أذهب إليه إلا لأنني كنت أشعر بعدم الارتياح الشديد.
I didn't want to disturb your sleep.
لم أكن أرغب في إزعاج نومك.
Actually, if you had called,
في الواقع، لو كنت قد اتصلت،
I would have come over.
كنت سأزوركم.
To play well on the field,
لتقديم أداء جيد في الملعب،
you need to at least ensure your body is healthy.
يجب عليك على الأقل التأكد من أن جسمك يتمتع بصحة جيدة.
I'll be in the living room.
سأكون في غرفة المعيشة.
If you feel unwell,
إذا شعرت بتوعك،
just call me anytime.
اتصل بي في أي وقت.
We meet again.
نلتقي مجدداً.
Teacher Li
المعلمة لي
He said he's Xiao Si's friend.
قال إنه صديق شياو سي.
I didn't know who he was then.
لم أكن أعرف من هو حينها.
Don't try to get too close.
لا تحاول الاقتراب كثيراً.
You all saw that kid.
لقد رأيتم جميعاً ذلك الطفل.
He seemed so clueless.
بدا وكأنه لا يفقه شيئاً.
Don't let your guard down.
لا تتهاون في حذرك.
Think about what we researched.
فكر فيما بحثنا عنه.
A comprehensive tactical response.
استجابة تكتيكية شاملة.
Those focused on team play, think team play.
أولئك الذين يركزون على اللعب الجماعي، يفكرون في اللعب الجماعي.
Those focused on individual play, think individual play.
أولئك الذين يركزون على اللعب الفردي، فليفكروا في اللعب الفردي.
Okay.
تمام.
Coach.
مدرب.
His hand injury should hold up for this match.
من المتوقع أن يستمر تعافيه من إصابة يده في هذه المباراة.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Okay, give it to me.
حسناً، أعطني إياه.
Li Youen
لي يوين
I really didn't expect this.
لم أتوقع هذا حقاً.
So you're Zhai Qiuyu's
إذن أنت تشاي كيويو
team doctor?
طبيب الفريق؟
I didn't expect that either.
لم أتوقع ذلك أيضاً.
A team doctor can switch to being an athlete.
يمكن لطبيب الفريق أن يتحول إلى رياضي.
Don't rush off.
لا تتعجل في المغادرة.
Everyone's so busy.
الجميع مشغولون للغاية.
You still have time to chat with an old acquaintance.
لا يزال لديك الوقت للدردشة مع أحد معارفك القدامى.
Get back to work.
عد إلى العمل.
I don't care what your intentions are,
لا يهمني ما هي نواياك،
but I'm warning you,
لكنني أحذرك،
stay away from my people.
ابتعد عن قومي.
They really are your people.
إنهم حقاً من أهلك.
Let me help you.
دعني أساعدك.
Don't bother me here.
لا تزعجني هنا.
We haven't settled the score from earlier.
لم نحسم الأمر بعد.
Gu Hao,
قو هاو,
take him to the lounge.
اصطحبه إلى الصالة.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I'll walk myself.
سأذهب بنفسي.
Zhai Qiuyu wins the second round.
Zhai Qiuyu يفوز بالجولة الثانية.
Zhai Qiuyu and Chen Mo are now tied.
Zhai Qiuyu و Chen Mo مقيدان الآن.
That's great!
هذا رائع!
Teacher Li,
المعلمة لي،
Qiuyu's right elbow is acting up again.
بدأ مرفق تشيو يو الأيمن يؤلمه مرة أخرى.
Can you come quickly and help him?
هل يمكنك المجيء بسرعة ومساعدته؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Didn't you win the second round?
ألم تفز بالجولة الثانية؟
We fell into their trap.
لقد وقعنا في فخهم.
Chen Mo kept forcing Qiuyu to use his backhand.
استمر تشين مو في إجبار تشيو يو على استخدام ضربته الخلفية.
He can't hold on much longer.
لم يعد بإمكانه الصمود لفترة أطول.
Teacher Li, slow down.
يا معلم لي، تمهل.
Just bear with it.
تحمّل الأمر.
You
أنت
That's good.
هذا جيد.
Okay.
تمام.
Go, go, Brother Yu!
انطلق، انطلق يا أخي يو!
Come on, come on!
هيا، هيا!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I'll head back to the lounge first.
سأعود إلى الصالة أولاً.
Zhai Qiuyu has now reached match point.
وصل تشاي تشيو يو الآن إلى نقطة المباراة.
He just needs to win one more point
يحتاج فقط إلى الفوز بنقطة واحدة أخرى
to win this match.
للفوز بهذه المباراة.
What a shame.
يا للعار.
If Chen Mo wins one more point,
إذا فاز تشين مو بنقطة أخرى،
the score will be tied again.
ستتعادل النتيجة مرة أخرى.
Is there something wrong with Zhai Qiuyu's racket?
هل هناك خلل ما في مضرب تشاي تشيويو؟
Zhai Qiuyu has called a timeout to change his racket.
طلب تشاي تشيو يو استراحة لتغيير مضربه.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Gu Hao
قو هاو
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
Teacher Li
المعلمة لي
Qiu Yu's string broke.
انقطع خيط تشيو يو.
Quick, get his spare racket.
أسرع، أحضر مضربه الاحتياطي.
I'm coming right now.
أنا قادم الآن.
Where's the racket?
أين المضرب؟
Go, go, go, Yu Ge!
انطلق، انطلق، انطلق يا جي!
Teacher Li
المعلمة لي
You shouldn't go back.
لا يجب عليك العودة.
Please, have a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
What a terrible racket.
يا لها من ضجة فظيعة.
It's not worn out.
إنها ليست بالية.
Someone tampered with it.
لقد عبث به أحدهم.
Why would the spare racket have this problem?
لماذا قد تواجه المضربة الاحتياطية هذه المشكلة؟
I took it out to check before the match.
أخرجته لأتأكد قبل المباراة.
It was fine.
كان الأمر على ما يرام.
And I had Coach Wang check it too.
وطلبت من المدرب وانغ أن يفحصه أيضاً.
Right.
يمين.
I definitely checked it.
لقد تحققت من ذلك بالتأكيد.
How could this happen?
كيف يمكن أن يحدث هذا؟
Who did this?
من فعل هذا؟
The spare racket was in the lounge.
كان المضرب الاحتياطي في الصالة.
It was Li Youen who brought it onto the court.
كان لي يوين هو من أدخلها إلى الملعب.
The spare racket might have been in the lounge
ربما كان المضرب الاحتياطي موجودًا في الصالة
and deliberately damaged.
وتم إتلافها عمداً.
It wasn't necessarily Teacher Li.
لم يكن بالضرورة المعلم لي.
Who else went into the lounge?
من دخل الصالة أيضاً؟
No one else.
لا أحد غيري.
Then it must have been you in the lounge.
إذن لا بد أنك كنت أنت في الصالة.
Me?
أنا؟
It wasn't me.
لم أكن أنا.
Zhai Qiuyu
تشاي كيويو
It really wasn't me.
لم أكن أنا حقاً.
You'd better explain.
من الأفضل أن تشرح.
Why was the initial injury report handled by you
لماذا تم التعامل مع تقرير الإصابة الأولي من قبلك؟
and then leaked to the media?
ثم تم تسريبها إلى وسائل الإعلام؟
Now the racket is the same.
والآن، الوضع كما هو.
Everything
كل شئ
happened after you joined the club.
حدث ذلك بعد انضمامك إلى النادي.
Li Youen,
لي يوين,
I can't cover for you anymore.
لم أعد أستطيع أن أغطي عليك.
You'd better explain it all clearly.
من الأفضل أن تشرح كل شيء بوضوح.
And
و
it seems you've known Chen Mo for a long time.
يبدو أنك تعرف تشين مو منذ فترة طويلة.
I even greeted him before the match.
بل إنني سلمت عليه قبل المباراة.
Now I have to doubt
الآن عليّ أن أشك
if Chen Mo bribed you.
إذا قام تشين مو برشوتك.
I have indeed met Chen Mo,
لقد التقيت بالفعل بتشن مو،
but
لكن
but I really didn't...
لكنني في الحقيقة لم أفعل...
How much money did Chen Mo give you?
كم من المال أعطاك تشين مو؟
Please believe me.
صدقني من فضلك.
I didn't.
لم أكن.
I don't want to see you again.
لا أريد رؤيتك مرة أخرى.
Qiu Yu, Brother Qiu Yu, Qiu Yu.
تشيو يو، الأخ تشيو يو، تشيو يو.